https://www.isabellevets.co.uk/privacy-policy/

01481 723863
MenuHomeAppointmentsEmergency AppointmentBook an Appointment OnlineRegister Your Pet ClosePet Care SupportPet Health ClubPet InsuranceEquine Health Club CloseCare AdviceCare Advice for DogsHealth TipsDental Care in my DogExercising my DogFeeding my DogTeeth and diet in my dogOther Useful TipsAnaesthetics in my dogBehaviour in my dogBreeding my dogFirst aid for dogsInsuring your dogLosing my dogMicrochipping my dogNeutering my dogTick RemovalVaccinating my dogPet TravelPet TravelThe Pet Travel Scheme for dogsAilments and AfflictionsCanine Hay FeverFlea control in my dogRoundworms in my dogTapeworms in my dogEye worm Infection in my dog CloseCare Advice for CatsHealth TipsDental Care in my CatFeeding my CatMy Cat’s Teeth and DietWorming my CatOther Useful TipsAnaesthetics in my catBirth control in my catFirst aid for catsFlea control in my catFurballs in my catSocialising my catPet TravelThe Pet Travel Scheme for catsAilments and AfflictionsDiarrhoea in my catFeline Hay FeverFeline infectious peritonitis (FIP)Feline Leukaemia (FeLv)Parasitic skin disease in my catRoundworms in my catTapeworms in my catToxoplasmosis in my catVomiting in my cat CloseCare Advice for RabbitsHealthy TipsAnaesthetics in my rabbitFeeding my rabbitKeeping my rabbit healthyNeutering my rabbitAilments and AfflictionsDental disease in my rabbitFly strike in my rabbitMyxomatosis in rabbitsRespiratory disease in my rabbitViral Haemorrhagic Disease CloseCare Advice for HorsesHealth TipsDental care in my horseOther Useful TipsInsuring my horseMeasuring a horseVetting a horse for purchaseAilments and AfflictionsAtypical MyopathyEquine influenza vaccinationLaminitisMud FeverEquine AsthmaWorm control in my horseWounds Close CloseEquineEquine Health Club CloseOur PracticeOur Dedicated TeamCT Scanner TeamHydrotherapy Service TeamInterested in a Veterinary Career?Job VacanciesPhoto Wall CloseNewsContact Us
Search
Search
Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy applies to the www.isabellevets.co.uk web site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before viewing the Isabelle Vets website further. Usage of the website is conditional upon you agreeing to be bound by this Privacy Policy.
Your personal information is important to us
Isabelle Vets recognises the importance of your privacy, and that you have a right to control how your personal information is collected and used. This Privacy Policy is intended to comply with GDPR.
Collecting information about you
Isabelle Vets will not collect any personal information about you without your consent. We only collect personal information that you tell us about yourself and information about how you use our website: e.g. when we ask for information such as your e-mail address, name, address and phone number. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that contact.
Using and disclosing your personal information
Isabelle Vets will not use or disclose any information, unless requested by you, as required by law or if we believe it necessary to provide you with a service you have requested. We may also do so to protect the rights, property or personal safety of another client, any member of the public or Isabelle Vets. We may also send you information which you have requested. We will not otherwise disclose it to other parties without your consent.
When we communicate with you
We may contact you at the e-mail or other address which you provide to us in order to provide you with updated information about our website or provide you with other information about our services. If you do not wish to receive this, you may have your name removed from our list by contacting us by email using the contact form or in writing. Please allow seven days for this to be processed.
The information we keep about you
If at any time you want to know exactly what personal information we hold about you, you can access your record by contacting us by email using the contact form or in writing. If you believe that your personal information is inaccurate or out of date, you can email us using the contact form or in writing and request your information be amended by us. If you wish to have your personal information deleted, we will take all reasonable and legal steps to delete it.
Storage and security of your personal information
Isabelle Vets will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date.
Isabelle Vets and links to other websites
Isabelle Vets provides links to external websites. These linked sites are not under the control of Isabelle Vets, and we are not responsible for the conduct of entities linked to our website.
Future changes
Isabelle Vets conducts regular reviews of all policies to ensure legal compliance and to reflect staff & customer feedback. Because of this, Isabelle Vets reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version of the policy on our website. The amended Privacy Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change.
We use anonymous cookies for various purposes including analytics and personalized marketing. By continuing to use the service, you agree to our use of cookies.
I agree
